<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on Miller-Jensen Lab at Yale</title><link>/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Miller-Jensen Lab at Yale</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:06:28 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kathryn co-organizes Systems Immunology conference</title><link>/news/cshl-systems-immunology-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/cshl-systems-immunology-2021/</guid><description>Kathryn co-organized the second Systems Immunology conference at Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory. Alas, due to the Covid-19 crisis, the conference was virtual this year. The conference included three days of amazing cross-disciplinary research.</description></item><item><title>Yale lab observes how macrophages respond to conflicting signals</title><link>/news/ydn-understanding-immune-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/ydn-understanding-immune-systems/</guid><description>Our lab was featured in today&amp;rsquo;s Yale Daily News: Understanding our immune systems: Yale lab observes how macrophages respond to conflicting signals. The article describes some of Andrés and Ilana&amp;rsquo;s work that was recently published in Nature Communications.</description></item><item><title>Researchers Aim to Decode Communications Within a Tumor</title><link>/news/yem-cellular-chatter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/yem-cellular-chatter/</guid><description>Our lab was featured in today&amp;rsquo;s Yale Engineering Magazine: &amp;lsquo;Cellular Chatter&amp;rsquo;: Researchers Aim to Decode Communications Within a Tumor. The article describes our lab&amp;rsquo;s work with the Marcus Bosenberg lab and our recent grant funded by the National Cancer Institute.</description></item><item><title>Yale researchers root out latent HIV viruses</title><link>/news/nci-grant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/nci-grant/</guid><description>Our lab was recently awarded a $2.8M grant from the National Cancer Institute to support our work with the Bosenberg lab through the Yale Cancer Center. We are, of course, enormously grateful for NCI&amp;rsquo;s support for this important work in which we&amp;rsquo;ll be modeling and evaluating cytokine signaling related to cancer immunotherapy.</description></item><item><title>Kathryn Speaks at U of British Columbia</title><link>/news/kathryn-speaks-at-ubc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 21:14:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/kathryn-speaks-at-ubc/</guid><description>Kathryn gave the SBME Seminar at the University of British Columbia, School of Biomedical Engineering (Vancouver Campus). She spoke about our work on single-cell analysis of macrophage heterogeneity.</description></item><item><title>Kathryn speaks at Pitt/CMU</title><link>/news/kathryn-speaks-at-cmu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 21:17:32 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/kathryn-speaks-at-cmu/</guid><description>Content here Kathryn spoke at Pitt and CMU in their joint Ph.D. Program in Computational Biology and the Department of Computational and Systems Biology Seminar. She discussed our group&amp;rsquo;s work exploring regulation of HIV latency with single-cell systems biology.</description></item><item><title>Congrats, Dr. Muñoz-Rojas!</title><link>/news/andres-defends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 15:14:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/andres-defends/</guid><description>Andrés successfully defended his thesis, &amp;ldquo;Analysis of macrophage polarization: single-cell responses in controlled and tumor microenvironments&amp;rdquo;. Congrats!</description></item><item><title>Yale researchers root out latent HIV viruses</title><link>/news/ydn-rooting-out-latency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/ydn-rooting-out-latency/</guid><description>Our lab was featured in today&amp;rsquo;s Yale Daily News: Yale researchers root out latent HIV viruses. The article describes Arvind and Victor&amp;rsquo;s work on HIV latency that was recently published in Scientific Reports.</description></item><item><title>Linda Fong Defends</title><link>/news/linda-fong-defends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 15:12:38 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/linda-fong-defends/</guid><description>Linda successfully defended her thesis, &amp;ldquo;Data-Driven Analysis of Phospho-Signaling Network Responses Enables Latent HIV-Infected T Cell Targeting&amp;rdquo;. Congrats!</description></item><item><title>Elise is awarded a PEB Training grant</title><link>/news/elise-awarded-peb-training-grant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 15:10:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/elise-awarded-peb-training-grant/</guid><description>Elise Bullock was awarded a slot on Yale&amp;rsquo;s NIH T32 Training grant supporting the Integrated Graduate Program in Physical and Engineering Biology.</description></item><item><title>Amanda is awarded the NSF fellowship</title><link>/news/amanda-nsf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/amanda-nsf/</guid><description>Amanda Alexander was awarded a Graduate Student Research Fellowship from the National Science Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Miller-Jensen lab featured in Yale Scientific</title><link>/news/lab-featured-in-yale-scientific/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 21:25:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/lab-featured-in-yale-scientific/</guid><description>In &amp;ldquo;Last Barrier to a Cure HIV&amp;rdquo;, Yale Scientific Magazine speaks about HIV latency with Kathryn and she describes our lab&amp;rsquo;s work on HIV &amp;ldquo;shock and kill&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Yale researchers root out latent HIV viruses</title><link>/news/ydn-systems-biology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 15:06:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/ydn-systems-biology/</guid><description>Our lab was featured in this month&amp;rsquo;s Yale Engineering Magazine and today&amp;rsquo;s Yale News: Yale researchers bring an engineering approach to systems biology efforts. The article describes some of our work with the Levchenko, Fan, and Murrell labs at Yale.</description></item><item><title>Ramesh's device in the news</title><link>/news/ramesh-device-in-the-news/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 15:04:56 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/ramesh-device-in-the-news/</guid><description>Ramesh&amp;rsquo;s device is featured in SciTechDaily.</description></item><item><title>Ramesh, Victor, and Arvind's paper is published in Integrative Biology</title><link>/news/ramesh-integrative-biology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 15:00:12 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/ramesh-integrative-biology/</guid><description>Ramesh designed a simple microfluidic device to trap an array of single T cells and then they used it to image noisy activation of latent HIV.</description></item><item><title>Qiong's and Yao's paper is published in Science Signaling</title><link>/news/science-signaling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 14:57:25 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/science-signaling/</guid><description>Qiong and Yao compared data from isolated single-cell assays to data from populations of cells to demonstrate that paracrine signaling is essential for stimulating a full LPS secretion response in macrophages. Markus applied data-driven modeling of the single-cell data to identify the most crucial paracrine signals regulating the response.</description></item><item><title>Students Present at HIV Keystone conference</title><link>/news/students-present-at-keystone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 14:51:41 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/students-present-at-keystone/</guid><description>Linda, Victor, and Arvind presented posters at the recent Keystone conference, Mechanisms of HIV Persistence: Implications for a Cure.</description></item><item><title>Kathryn Receives Nsf Career Award</title><link>/news/kathryn-receives-nsf-career-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 14:41:31 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/kathryn-receives-nsf-career-award/</guid><description>Kathryn was selected to receive the 2015 NSF CAREER Award for our group&amp;rsquo;s project, &amp;ldquo;Reverse Engineering the Inflammatory Signaling Network from Single-Cell Data.&amp;rdquo; The award provides $500,000 in funding to researchers who exemplify the role of teacher-scholars. The CAREER Award is the NSF’s most prestigious award for junior faculty.
This project examines why genetically identical macrophages — the first responders in the immune system — vary in how strongly they respond to the presence of pathogens by secreting pro-inflammatory &amp;ldquo;danger signals.</description></item><item><title>Kathryn featured in Fusion "genius" segment</title><link>/news/kathryn-featured-in-fusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 21:22:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>/news/kathryn-featured-in-fusion/</guid><description>Kathryn was featured on Fusion&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;genius&amp;rdquo; segment. In this short video she describes the counterintuitive ‘shock and kill’ method to curing HIV.</description></item></channel></rss>