<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>People on Miller-Jensen Lab at Yale</title><link>/people/</link><description>Recent content in People on Miller-Jensen Lab at Yale</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/people/amanda-alexander/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/amanda-alexander/</guid><description>Amanda is investigating spatial and temporal regulation of cell-to-cell heterogeneity in the inflammatory response in macrophages. She is interested in how dysregulation of intercellular heterogeneity in inflammation may contribute to autoimmune diseases. Amanda is supported by an NSF Graduate Research Fellowship. She received her Bachelor’s degree in Mathematics from Spelman College with additional coursework in Biomedical Engineering at the Georgia Institute of Technology.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/andres-munoz-rojas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/andres-munoz-rojas/</guid><description>Andrés is investigating the paradoxical role of macrophages in promoting and destroying tumors. Using a novel microfluidic device, he is studying the signaling dynamics of single macrophages and correlating it to downstream protein secretion signatures in the same single cell. His interests include cancer immunology, microscopy, systems biology and signal transduction. Andrés received his Bachelor’s degree in Bioengineering from the University of Pennsylvania with a minor in Music.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/arvind-chavali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/arvind-chavali/</guid><description>Arvind is investigating the role of cell-to-cell heterogeneity in the activation of latent HIV proviruses. His interests lie in computational modeling and systems analysis. Arvind received his PhD in biomedical engineering from the University of Virginia.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/elise-bullock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/elise-bullock/</guid><description>Elise studies signaling and transcriptional regulation of HIV latency using computational and experimental approaches. Her goal is to understand how signaling and transcriptional heterogeneity control viral phenotypes when coupled to feedback control. Her interests include systems biology, computational modeling, and synthetic biological circuits. Elise is a member of the Integrated Graduate Program in Physical and Engineering Biology and is supported by the program’s NIH T32 training grant. She received her Bachelor’s degree in Biomedical Engineering from the University of Texas at Dallas.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/endah-sulistijo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/endah-sulistijo/</guid><description>Endah got her Ph.D. in Biochemistry from Rice University. She is currently involved to two research projects: (1) Characterization of protein phosphorylation signatures in latent HIV-infected cells and non-infected cells, and (2) Optimization of microfluidic techniques for detection of cell signaling proteins at single-cell level.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/ilana-kelsey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/ilana-kelsey/</guid><description>Ilana is interested in the polarization process of macrophages, specifically how individual cells activate and regulate their polarization responses when they encounter complex or conflicting cues from the environment. Using live-cell microscopy and flow cytometry, she is investigating the signaling events, gene transcription, and protein production of various polarization pathways to elucidate the plasticity and mechanism of polarization decisions in complex environments, such as might be encountered in the tumor microenvironment.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/laura-kellman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/laura-kellman/</guid><description>Laura is studying the role of p38 kinase signaling in the regulation of IL-6 following TLR stimulation. She uses both single-cell and cell-population approaches to understand how intercellular signaling heterogeneity translates to variability in cytokine secretion. Laura received her Bachelor’s degree in Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology from Yale University.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/linda-fong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/linda-fong/</guid><description>Linda&amp;rsquo;s research focuses on the temporal dynamics of phosphoproteins in the reactivation of latent HIV. Through systems analysis and multivariate regression modeling, her work aims to elucidate key signaling pathways which can predict network responses to pharmacologic intervention. Her research interests involve using data-driven models of cell signaling to approach problems in oncology and infectious diseases. Linda earned her BS from MIT in Biological Engineering (Course XX) with a minor in Science, Technology, and Society and a concentration in Ethics.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/markus-eisele/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/markus-eisele/</guid><description>Markus is studying the different behavior of single cells under LPS stress compared to cells in a population. He is using computational modeling and systems analysis to explore TLR4 signaling. Markus is a Master’s student in Stuttgart, Germany and is visiting Yale University for one year.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/qiong-xue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/qiong-xue/</guid><description>Qiong joined the Miller-Jensen lab from Texas A&amp;amp;M with a background in inflammation and infectious diseases. She is investigating cytokine/chemokine secretion signatures of both a cell population and single cells and excited to apply systems analysis to single cell inflammatory responses.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/ramesh-ramji/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/ramesh-ramji/</guid><description>Ramesh likes to invent novel integrated micro analytical devices for biological applications. With a PhD in bioengineering (microfluidic cell based assays) from the National University of Singapore (NUS), he dwells into areas including nanobiotechnology, bioimaging, analytical chemistry and instrumentation. He is currently developing a high throughput multiplexed microfluidic device to quantify signaling dynamics and endpoint protein secretion at the &amp;ldquo;single cell&amp;rdquo; level.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/victor-bass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/victor-bass/</guid><description>Victor studies how single cell heterogeneity in NF-kB dynamics affects transcription of inflammatory genes in different chromatin environments. He uses a combination of live-cell imaging and single molecule fluorescence in situ hybridization to measure NF-κB dynamics and quantify transcript output in the same single cells. His research interests include single-cell heterogeneity, signal transduction, and fluorescence microscopy. He received his Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Biological Sciences from Carnegie Mellon University with a minor in Chemistry.</description></item><item><title/><link>/people/victor-wong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/victor-wong/</guid><description>Victor is studying how cell-to-cell heterogeneity in NF-kB dynamics and chromatin environment combine to regulate transcriptional activation of latent HIV. He is using a combination of live-cell imaging and single molecular fluorescence in situ hybridization (smFISH) to observe latent HIV activation in single cells. His interests include molecular biology, microscopy, biological noise and signal transduction. Victor received his Bachelor’s degree in Biology from the University of Pennsylvania.</description></item></channel></rss>